hamidashita kaze wo atsumete mitai na
I want to try and gather the unrestrained winds
nami no saki tsutatte kanata e kaketeku
I'll run toward the horizon alongside the wave crests
kakugo wa kimatteru
I've made my decision
michi wa tookutemo
even if there's a long way to go on that road
egaita mirai e tsudzuiteru
I'll continue towards the future I've planned
toki ga bokura wo sekashite kodou ga supiido agetetta
time rushes us, the heartbeat speeds up
yume no naka de mezametemo onaji hikari wo sagashita
when I woke in the middle of a dream, I kept searching for that same light
kagayaku hoshizora no shita kazoekirenai seiza to kage
under the shining star-lit sky, with countless constellations and shadows
sono saki ni kimi wa nani wo nani wo mitsumete iru darou
there was something beyond that, what were you gazing at?
nani wo mitsumete iru darou
what were you gazing at?
Our mission this time around
is a rough one.
Can you do it, Lee?
I'll be okay! I can go anytime.
Now that's my protege!
Let's go, Lee!
Right, Guy-sensei!
They're off!
Those large bags no doubt mean
an overnight expedition mission.
To think we'd encounter the ideal pair
so quickly. We're lucky.
Then it's settled.
Right. Starting operation.
To infilrtra... Whoa!
Heavy! Get off, you idiot.
To... infiltrate...
the super elite hidden village...
the Village Hidden in Leaves!
Meeting the
Rare Visitors
Wow, we look just like those two!
Naturally. We refined
our Disguise Jutsu for this very day.
We're after the classified information
of the Leaf...
Right!
We'll be famous if this goes well!
The idea is to win distinction
for our village.
Then we'll get tons of missions
and we'll be the village heroes!
Village Heroes! Mondai and Poccha!
All right.
As of this moment, my name's Guy.
The Leaf Ninja, "Mondai Guy"!
And I'm the protege, "Poccha Lee"!
Let's go, Lee.
Yes, Guy-sensei!
Nothing like a large village, sure enough!
Wow, everyone's like a Ninja.
Hey! Don't be looking all about so much!
Listen up.
There's a chief in this village
called the "Hokage."
No doubt classified information
is concentrated where that person is.
— I see.
— If I remember correctly,
that person's in a building easy to spot
with a "Fire" mark on it or something.
— There it is!
— That's it!
What about Hokage-sama's house?
— Yikes!
Hi.
Nothing special! We're not after Leaf
classified information or any... Any...
Are you an idiot?!
It's nothing at all!
Is that so?
Look, we've got to act naturally here.
Right...
Hi. I'm Guy.
I'm Lee.
Guy and Lee, eh?
Don't you guys have
a different atmosphere than usual?
No. It's your imagination!
No, I feel like something's different...
Oh, there's a kite up there flying
while eating a pork cutlet rice bowl!
What? Where? Where?
What? There's no kite anywhere.
Hey, what?
Jeez, that Ninja has to go
and stand behind us
without any sign of his presence.
But it seems we fooled him good.
Our Disguise Jutsu is perfect,
sure enough.
Say, infiltration is kind of easy,
isn't it?!
The Leaf isn't worth fearing!
Guy and Lee imposters are
prowling around the village?
And to think they'd enter the village
in disguises
without even using Transformation Jutsu.
Are they really Ninja?
Weird people find their way in
when a village grows.
Well, it's nonsense, but I thought
I would at least report it for now.
Indeed, we can't just leave
intruders unchecked.
Shall we throw them out?
— No, leave them be.
— What?
It sounds interesting, doesn't it?
They're going to the trouble of
calling themselves Ninja of this village.
But...
We probably don't need to worry.
It's unlikely that anyone could be
fooled by such obvious imposters.
Come on, please.
Guy-sensei, Bushy Brow!
Pretty please with sugar on top!
Just the one day today would be fine!
Let me join your training!
Hey, what's with this guy all of a sudden?
He's probably a real acquaintance
of theirs, but...
Does he think we're going to do training?
I'll do anything!
I've always been interested in Taijutsu.
I mean... okay?! It's okay, right?
— Anyway, let's turn him away.
— Right.
No. Take a pass.
What? Why?!
Because our training is very harsh,
rough and difficult.
Difficult training, huh?
Ah, I'm getting even more fired up!
Please!
I won't get in your way, no matter what!
Come on.
— Absolutely not!
All right, since it's come to this!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Real body clones?!
And furthermore...
Harem Jutsu!
What?!
— What?!
Please.
— Okay!
What?!
Yes!
— No way.
Brother, why'd you say okay?
What's done is done,
so, it can't be helped, right?
Hey, Guy-sensei, Lee!
What's the deal, you two?
We're going to the farm today, right?
— Farm?
— What are you doing,
Letting your mind wander?
The person's waiting. Come on, hurry!
Hey!
Hey, wait!
What...?
I promised to plant rice
for the sake of training?
Not only that, all of this...
It's totally huge.
Gee, thanks. It's a big help,
you guys giving me a hand.
Please, don't worry about it.
They accepted this
on their own accord, so... Bye.
Why is this training?
I get it!
Indeed, I will use my body quite a bit
if I do this training.
So I can get in shape
while helping out, huh?
Guy-sensei, Bushy Brow!
I'll do my best!
Why's he that motivated?
Why should we have
to do this manual labor...?
Damn it. Anyway, let's get this over with!
You're right.
That's mean, brother!
Oh, sorry about that.
What?
Poccha?!
Come to think of it,
there are flying leeches
in the rice fields, so be careful.
Flying leeches?!
Worst-case scenario, it could be deadly.
Yikes.
Hey, Poccha!
Hang in there!
Just what I'd expect of Taijutsu training!
That was some intense rice planting!
That was a good workout!
We're done...
That was life-or-death...
Then shall we move on?
— A manure receptacle?!
Spread this in that field over there.
This is also training...?
Heavy... Smelly...
Why should I have
to do something like this?
Hey, you guys,
why don't you walk straight?
You can walk twice
the forward progress distance
if you move ahead while
walking left and right like this!
Oh, so that was it?
Then I'll also...
Like this?
It's really hard to balance like this!
Damn it!
Gee, I didn't realize at all that
there was a method of training like this.
Hey, watch it. Walk more over there...
What'd you say?
— What a nightmare.
— Forget about it.
Anyway, let's lose the kid right now.
As for you guys,
you still kind of smell bad.
— Shut up!
There you are, Guy-sensei, Lee.
Oh, Sakura.
Oh, Naruto. You're here, too?
As for me, I'm training together
with these two today.
Really?
— More importantly, is something up?
— Yeah...
Actually, I really wanted your help
with something, Guy-sensei, Lee.
— What?
— Your laundry blew away?
That's right.
It got caught in a bit of a high spot.
No. No way, no way.
We've got lots of work to do, so...
Come on! Here I'm asking precisely
because it's you guys.
Please, don't say no!
Sakura, if you're in that much trouble,
I could get it for you!
Okay, Guy-sensei?
Okay?!
Sure.
What a sheer cliff.
That's for sure. We'd be beyond help
if we were to fall from up there.
Right?
I don't quite have the confidence...
That means...
Yup! It's right above here.
Gee, as one would expect,
I don't think we could...
Isn't that great, Sakura?
For Guy-sensei, a cliff like this is
no different than a flat path.
That's encouraging.
It's a big help having an awesome Ninja
like you close by, Guy-sensei.
What?
Now, please.
Brother...
Damn it. Why is this happening?!
I don't want to die.
Damn it!
Hey, as for you guys,
why aren't you using the Chakra suction?
This is training for building up
muscular strength!
So, that's what it was?
Just what I'd expect of a Taijutsu user.
I never came up with deliberately
draining physical strength!
I really do learn a lot from
being with you, Sensei.
This jerk...
I'm... I'm going to die...
No!
That was close...!
Gee, sorry about that.
This jerk...
All right, we made it.
Don't look down!
Anyway, if we can just take
this back with us...
Damn it...
All right, I got it.
It won't come loose...
Hey, help me out here.
Right...
You little...!
Sensei, use suction with your Chakra!
This is nothing to me!
Look out!
For real? What?!
Guy-sensei! Bushy Brow!
I've had it...
Sensei, Bushy Brow!
That was awesome!
To do something like not
using Chakra suction. Awesome!
— Look you...!
Perfect timing, you guys.
Grandma Tsunade.
Actually, I've got something
I want to ask you guys to do.
My companion suddenly started
not feeling well, you see.
— Yikes, it's huge!
— It's huge!
It seems she's caught a cold.
It's a huge slug. Oh, as for this,
is it something like Chief Toad?
Well, that sounds about right.
However, as you can see,
we can't carelessly move her.
Sorry, could you guys look
after her for a while?
I'm very sorry.
Jeez, what a ridiculous guy.
Brother, at this rate we won't be able
to look for the confidential information.
Oh, that's right.
Shut up.
What are you moaning about?
You guys.
It couldn't be that you guys can't listen
to the words of me,
the Hokage, could it?
— This is the Hokage?
This is bad. To think the Hokage
was that fierce a person.
We're taking care of
her precious companion.
We might be able to get into
the Hokage estate surprisingly easily.
I wonder.
So, even Summoning animals
get sick, too...
It seems to be a light cold.
My nose itches, I have a sore throat,
and I feel weak or something...
Hey, I'm going to chill your forehead!
Thank you so much.
All right, here we go.
Oh, no. The itching...
What?!
— Wha...?!
— What?!
It's... It's melting...
Watch it, you!
I'm very sorry. I'll be more caref...
Guy-sensei! Bushy Brow!
You'll be in danger
if you don't move away from there!
My... My lower back...
You idiot!
I'm developing my dynamic vision
for narrowly evading danger!
Wha...?
That Sensei, he was training,
putting his life at risk
even at times like this...?
Even though that Bushy Brow guy's
training properly, as for me...!
I've woken up,
Guy-sensei, I'll train with you!
Let's do this!
Oh, the joints in my body hurt...
I feel like I'm going to fall apart...
Hey! Aren't you a slug?
What are you doing talking about joints?!
— Save us.
— Save us!
I've had it.
What's going on with this village...?
I'll die if I stay in a place like this
any longer.
Withdraw...
Right.
Who are you guys?
Why are you dressed
like my protege Lee...?
Damn it! Since it's come to this,
I don't give a damn anymore!
— Super Excellent Great Hyper Attack!
I don't really get it,
but it seems we just have to fight, huh?
So it seems.
Let's go, Lee!
Now, knockout technique!
— Double Dynamic Entry!
Damn it!
What did we go there for in the end?!
I really hate, I really hate...
— The likes of the Leaf!
Tamaya!
Lord knows where they came from,
but now they'll probably never
want to try that again.
You sure looked like
you were having fun, Tsunade-sama,
going so far as to summon Katsuyu.
Well, my adorable Genin
helped out as well, so...
Now, we've had our breather.
So, please, be getting back to work.
Oh, yes, ma'am.
But still... What was with that Naruto?
To think he seriously believed
those two were for real.
What was that all about?
Who knows...?
Hey!
Naruto.
— Someone who looked just like me now...
— Man, you guys got separated.
I didn't know what to do.
As for me, I was impressed!
You guys were really cool earlier!
I've learned of the intricacies
of Taijutsu or something...
A lot happened,
but I'll continue training right away!
Continue training?
So, come on,
let's continue the Taijutsu training!
Moron, moron, moron.
dokomademo tsudzuku michi ni wa ironna koto arunda ne
so many things happen on this endless road, right?
tsuyogari na kimi ga kyou wa juwaki koshi ni namida koe
although you're strong-willed your voice wavered on the phone today
donna yume oikakete kokomade kitan darou
what dreams did you chase to get here?
wakara na kunattari suru koto wa boku ni datte aru kara nee BABY
even I have times when I just don't understand baby
kimi ga namida no toki ni wa boku ga soba ni iru kara
when you're sad I'll be close to you
hanareba nare no yoru datte boku wa soba ni iru kara
even on nights when we're apart I'll be close to you
boku wa soba ni iru kara
I'll be close to you
Damn it! Why should a Ninja have
to do something like get rid of a ghost?!
We have no choice, right?
After all, a commission is a commission!
The ghost of a feudal lord, my butt?!
Th-That's ridiculous!
But they say it comes out at night!
A ghost warrior clad in a white armor!
N-No, I'm not afraid of it at all!
H-Hey! Behind you!
No!
I knew it! You ARE afraid!
Next time:
"A White Cursed Samurai."